seorankflicks.com 2012-04-01

# Privacy Policy - SEORankFlicks.com

#### Privacy Policy

**What information do we obtain?**  
Information is obtained by use when you sign up for SEO services. When ordering/registering on our site, you may be requested to enter your name, e-mail address, phone number and credit card information as appropriately as possible. You may, however, visit our site anonymously at any time.

As is done by most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to embellish your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website.

**How do we use information you submit?**  
We use the information obtained from you in one of the following ways:   
To customize your experience (information you provide helps us to respond to your individual needs in a better way)  
To enhance our website (we continuously work to embellish our website offerings based on the information and feedback we obtain from you)  
To transfer periodic emails  
Customer will not receive any continual email solicitation from the company, unless the customer agrees to the solicitation at checkout, or through a double opt-in process. And, if the customer does consent to receive email from the company, the company agrees to have a simple unsubscribe option available, along with unsubscribe instructions in every email.

**How do we safeguard your information?**  
We implement an array of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.

After a transaction, your private information (credit card number, billing address, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to appropriately charge for SEORankFlicks services.  
**  
Do we reveal any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Terms and Conditions**  
You are requested to visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at:

**Your Consent**  
When you use our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Alterations to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to alter our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any queries regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Testimonial

SEORankFlicks has done an impeccable job by helping my company achieve top rankings in search engines for many competitive keywords relevant to my industry . My site now ranks in Google for keywords among millions of competing pages. I am happy that I chose them for my SEO needs!

**Technotalks.com**

#### Awards
